cradlepoint.com 2019-07-02

# Privacy Policy | Cradlepoint

Your privacy is important to Cradlepoint, Inc. Cradlepoint recognizes and appreciates the responsible use of information collected on its websites and by its products and services. Cradlepoint is committed to protecting your data and takes all reasonable precautions to safeguard its confidentiality. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect, how we use this information, with whom it is shared, and how it is stored when you visit the Cradlepoint, Inc. websites and use our products and services.  

### European Union (EU) & United Kingdom (UK) Residents

View Cradlepoint’s Privacy Policy relating to the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

* * *

## The Information We Collect

When you submit personal information to Cradlepoint, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Cradlepoint and its affiliates and subsidiaries maintain offices including, without limitation, the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of Cradlepoint. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties.

### Websites, Marketing Emails, or Mobile Apps

We automatically collect certain information when you use or access our websites to help us manage our relationship with you.  The following personal information may be collected:

  * Contact details, such as name, company title, mailing address, email address, and phone number
  * Shipping and billing information, including payment information
  * Your transaction history
  * Your interaction with Cradlepoint web pages:  documents downloaded, pages visited, webinar registration and attendance;
  * Information provided to Cradlepoint to receive technical assistance or during customer service interactions;
  * Information about your computer or device, including browser type and settings, version number, time zone setting.  Also, visitors’ IP address, device ID, operating system, browser type and version number, time zone setting.

### Products & Services

Regarding your organization’s deployment of Cradlepoint products and services, we may collect certain data relating to the performance and configuration of the Cradlepoint products and services, and our customer’s and their end-user’s consumption of and interaction and use of such products and services (“Usage Data”).  Usage Data is generally technical information obtained from product software or systems hosting the services, devices accessing these products and services and/or log files generated during such use. Usage Data does not include any customer content (e.g. Web traffic) transferred through Cradlepoint products or services.

Some Cradlepoint products and services automatically collect and store certain Usage Data through cookies, pixel tags and other similar tracking technologies that uniquely identify a browser or device. For additional information about our use of cookies and other similar tracking technologies, please refer to our Use Of Cookies section below.

Cradlepoint may monitor customer’s use of subscription services and compile customer data with other data in an aggregate and anonymous manor to derive statistical and performance information relating to the provision and operation of the subscription services.  Cradlepoint may make such information publicly available provided such information does not include any data that would enable the identification of customer or customer data or the disclosure of customer confidential information.  Cradlepoint retains all rights, title and interest in and to such statistical and performance information.

### How Your Data is Used

  * To provide you with the website page;
  * To respond to your requests or provide information requested by you;
  * To better understand our customers and end-users and the way they use and interact with our website;
  * To provide a personalized experience, and implement the preferences you request;
  * To provide you with marketing and promotional communications (where this is in accordance with the law);
  * To determine the effectiveness of marketing and promotional campaigns;
  * To interact with you on third party social networks (subject to that network’s terms of use);
  * To communicate with you about our events or our partner events;  
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered between you and Cradlepoint
  * To provide you with the information, products and services that you request from Cradlepoint;
  * To provide you with additional information about other products and services Cradlepoint offers;
  * To notify you about changes to Cradlepoint’s products and services;
  * To ensure that content from Cradlepoint web sites is presented in the most effective manner; and
  * To operate, support and improve the products and services you have purchased or to which you have subscribed.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data (text file) that a website asks your browser to store on your device in order to remember information about you, such as your language preference or login information. Those cookies are set by Cradlepoint and called first party cookies.

Cradlepoint uses cookies to assist in navigation of our web sites and to enable use of our products and services.  Cradlepoint also uses third party cookies for our advertising and marketing efforts.

### Sharing Your Information

Cradlepoint may share any information it collects with selected third parties including:

  * Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors required for the provision of the products and services;
  * Channel partners to facilitate purchase or subscription of Cradlepoint products and services;
  * Financial institutions for the purposes of credit assessment and scoring where this is a condition of entering into a contract with you.

Cradlepoint may also disclose your information:

  * In response to court orders, subpoenas, governmental requests or other legal process or to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions of supply and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Cradlepoint, our customers, or others (and this includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction); and
  * In the event of a merger, acquisition or sale of all or substantially all of Cradlepoint’s assets to a third party, in which case personal data held by Cradlepoint about you will be transferred to such party.

### Changes to the Statement of Privacy

Cradlepoint reserves the right to change its practices concerning information gathered from visitors to Cradlepoint’s web sites and users of Cradlepoint products and services. If such changes occur, this Privacy Policy will be updated. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to Cradlepoint’s Privacy Policy.  

## Contact Us

If you have any questions in relation to this Privacy Policy or how Cradlepoint collects, uses, or stores your data, you can contact us at:

  * Phone: +1 855 813 3385
  * Address: Cradlepoint, Inc., 1111 W. Jefferson Street, Suite 400, Boise, ID 83702-5389, Attn: Legal Department
  * Email at: [privacy@cradlepoint.com ](mailto:privacy@cradlepoint.com)

Cradlepoint welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy.
